哦  嗯
Oh. Mm.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hey.
你应该尝尝这块起司蛋糕
You have got to try this cheesecake.
你知道   我的牙不能吃太甜的东西
Oh, you know, I'm not that much of a sweet tooth--
我的天啊  好香浓
Oh, my God, it's so creamy. Oh.
那是我吃过的最棒的起司蛋糕
Oh, my God. That's the best cheesecake I've ever had.
你在哪里买到它
Where did you get this?
我到家时它就已经放在门口了  应该是有人寄给我们的
It was at the front door when I got home. Somebody sent it to us.
钱德   收件人可不是你
Chandler, this isn't addressed to you.
收件人是楼下的布雷曼太太
This is addressed to Mrs. Braverman downstairs.
小偷
Thief.
我没看名子就打开盒子了
I didn't read the box before I opened it...
盒子已经打开   就无法退还了
...and you can't return a box after you opened it.
为什么  因为它太好吃了
Why not? Because it's too delicious.
钱德  你偷了这个起司蛋糕   是犯错的
Chandler, you stole this cheesecake. That is wrong.
不  不  没关系的
No, no, no, it is going to be okay...
因为布雷曼太太会免费再收到一个
...because Mrs. Braverman is gonna send away for a free one.
那可是   双赢啊
And that way, we all win.
唯一的输家是大型起司蛋糕店
The only losers are the big cheesecake conglomerate:
"妈妈的小面包店"
"Mama's Little Bakery."
我觉得好难过
I feel terrible.
我是个大坏蛋  大坏蛋  大坏人
I'm a horrible, horrible, horrible person.
对不起  你说什么
Well, I'm sorry, what?
老友记  第七季  第11集  起司蛋糕
Friends  S07E11 The One With All The Cheesecakes
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
行了  我得走了  我今天工作很忙
All right, I should get going. Big day a work.
你们知道我怎么会昏迷不醒吗
You know how I'm in a coma?
今天他们要帮我做检查   结果发现我没有脑死亡
Today they do a test on me and it turns out I'm not brain-dead.
所以
So--
聪明先生
Ah-ah, Mr. Smarty-Pants.
没有脑死亡的是我演的角色
It's just my character that's not brain-dead.
菲比  今晚的事没取消吧
Hey, so Pheebs, still on for tonight?
当然  八点见  好的
Absolutely. Okay. All right, I'll see you at 8. Okay.
什么东西八点见
Oh, what's at 8?
我们约好吃晚餐
Oh, I have dinner plans with Joey.
我们大约一个月会约一次去讨论你们的事
We get together about once a month to discuss the rest of you guys.
哇  我真的不知道
Wow. Did not know that.
我能说  你今天看起来很漂亮吗
May I say how lovely you look today?
那当然
Duly noted.
那么  明天
Oh, so for tomorrow...
你要租辆车一起开过去吗
...do you want to rent a car and drive down together or what?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
芬妮表妹的婚礼  明晚啊
Cousin Frannie's wedding. It's tomorrow night.
你被邀请了
You were invited?
不
No.
我的天啊  我不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe this.
我以为他们只邀请了爸跟妈
I mean I knew Mom and Dad were invited. I thought that was it.
七岁到九岁  芬妮跟我形影不离
I mean, from the ages of 7 to 9, Frannie and I were inseparable.
或许九岁后  芬妮交了新朋友
Well, maybe since the age of 9, Frannie's made some new friends.
或许这只是个误会  我打电话去问雪若阿姨
Well l-look okay, it's probably just a mistake. Let me call Aunt Cheryl, okay?
或许他们邀请你了  只是请帖寄丢了
Maybe you are invited and the invitation just got lost in the mail.
你可以打电话告诉她  我们小时候
Yeah, well, you call her and tell her that, you know, when we were kids...
她的宝贝芬妮好几次想脱光我的衣服
...her precious little Frannie tried to undress me several times, okay?
要不是我阻止了她  她也结不了婚
If I hadn't stopped her, there probably wouldn't be a wedding to go to.
她也想脱我的衣服
She tried to undress me too.
我以前会帮葛兰表弟脱衣服
I used to undress my cousin Glenn.
乔瑟夫法兰西斯崔比亚尼   你回家了吗
Joseph Francis Tribbiani, are you home yet?
我想他还没有回家  怎么了
Um, I think he's still out. What's wrong?
我得告诉你   瑞秋凯伦葛林
Well, I'll tell you, Rachel Karen Green.
我跟乔伊今晚有约  他留了这张字条给我
I had plans with Joey tonight, and he left me this note.
"菲比  我没办法赴约  我有约会  待会再谈
"Pheebs, can't make it. Got a date. Talk to you later.
大爹地"
Big Daddy?
"大爹地"  那是我们之间的昵称
"Big Daddy"? Oh, that's a nickname we were trying out.
你知道什么样的昵称  不会跟别人重复吗  "罗斯原子超人"
Hey, you know what nickname never caught on? "The Ross-a-tron."
乔瑟夫法兰西斯回来了
Hey. Oh, here's Joseph Francis.
等一下  你干嘛叫我的全名
Whoa, what are you middle-naming me for'?
我给你留了字条
I left you a note.
那不是你放我鸽子的好理由
So what? That doesn't give you the right to ditch me.
如果你有机会上床  当然可以取消跟朋友的约会
Hey, you can cancel plans with friends if there's a possibility for sex.
菲比  他说的对  这是规则
Phoebe, he's right. That is the rule.
我无法接受这种事
I don't accept this rule.
我们约好后  我期待你会出现
When we make plans, I expect you to show up.
我不是你泡到马子前打发时间的代替品
Okay, I can't just be a way to kill time till you meet someone better.
男女朋友来来去去   但朋友是一辈子的
You know, boyfriends and girlfriends are gonna come and go, but this is for life.
我真的很抱歉   我不知道这对你来说那么重要
Wow. I'm so sorry. I had no idea it would bother you this much.
是啊  它的确很重要
Well, it does.
我可以弥补你吗
Okay, can I make it up to you? Huh?
对不起
I'm sorry.
明天晚上一起吃饭吧   我会自己付钱
How about dinner tomorrow night? I'll pay for myself.
好吧  你说服了我
Okay, you wore me down.
乔伊  既然你站在那边  就拿罐啤酒给 "罗斯原子超人"吧
Hey Joe, while you're over there, how about another beer for "The Ross-a-tron"?
"罗斯" 它又回来了
"Ross--" Is that back?
又有起司蛋糕
Hi. The other cheesecake came.
他们又把它送到这里了
They delivered it to the wrong address again.
把它送到楼下去   能有什么问题
So just bring it back downstairs. What's the problem?
我不知道该怎么说再见
I can't seem to say goodbye.
你是认真的吗  钱德  两天前我们才吃掉了一个蛋糕
Are you serious? Chandler, we ate an entire cheesecake two days ago...
你还想再吃啊
...and you want more?
喔  我已经忘记它的味道了
Well, I've forgotten what it tastes like, okay?
它是起司蛋糕   很好吃
It was cheesecake. It was fine.
它又香又浓   酥酥的饼干
It had a buttery, crumbly, graham-cracker crust...
还有味道非常浓郁
...with a very rich...
但不油腻的奶油起司
...yet light cream-cheese filling.
我的嘴巴全是口水
Wow, my whole mouth just filled with saliva. Ahem.
你知道吗  忘了它  我们只是饿了
Y'know what? Forget it. We are just hungry.
我们没吃午饭   所以头昏脑胀的
We have not had lunch. We are just light-headed.
那我们去吃午饭吧   忘了那个起司蛋糕吧
So let us go out and have lunch and forget about the cheesecake.
我们得把它还回去  才不会被诱惑
Yeah and we'll drop it off downstairs so that we're not tempted.
好主意  你要去哪儿吃午饭
Good idea. Where do you wanna go to lunch?
芝加哥小妈妈面包店
Mama's Little Bakery, Chicago, Illinois.
梅尔多米死了
Mel Torme died.
乔伊  那是一年前的报纸了
Joey, that paper's like a year old.
那就表示山姆古迪商店的大特卖结束了
Oh, does that mean the Sam Goody's sale is over?
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
我终于收到雪若阿姨的回音
So I finally heard back from Aunt Cheryl...
很明显地这不是误会
...and apparently it wasn't a mistake.
婚礼现场座位有限
Uh, there's limited seating in the hall--
座位有限  我是个瘦皮猴
Limited seating? I am just one tiny person.
对  但是她不知道
Well yeah, but she doesn't know that.
我是说上次她看到你
I mean, the last time she saw you...
你会把婚礼用的小椅子给压垮
...you would've turned one of those little wedding chairs into kindling.
"座位有限"  真是个烂藉口
"Limited seating." That's such a lame excuse.
那不是她不邀请我的原因
That's not the reason why she's not inviting me.
那有什么大不了的呢  我没办法观礼  只能去吃喜酒
What's the big deal? I wasn't even invited to the ceremony, just the reception.
如果这能让你觉得开心一点
And you know what? If it makes you feel any better...
琼安跟我只会去亮个相
...Joan and I will just make an appearance...
我们会提早离开  以示抗议
...and then we'll leave early as a sign of protest.
琼安  对  她是我的女伴
Joan? Yeah, Joan Tedeschi, my date.
她是语言学系的助教
She's an assistant professor in the Linguistics Department.
又高又漂亮
Tall, very beautiful.
虽然有些人说  别挑太魁梧的女孩
And despite what some people say, not broad-backed.
等一下  你收到的喜帖是 "请携伴参加"
Wait a minute. You got "Ross Geller and guest"?
我没有被邀请  你却可以"携伴参加"
I wasn't invited, and you got "and guest"?
对不起  我真的得解释罗斯的行为
Uh, excuse me, I do have to interrupt on Ross' behalf.
我想规则也适用在这里
I think the rule applies here y'know,
因为他有机会跟魁梧女人上床
Since he has a chance to get on broad-back--
她没有那么魁梧
Not broad-back!
等一下  你得带我去
Wait a minute. You're bringing me.
什么  我不能放琼安鸽子
What? I can't cancel on Joan.
为什么  你没有听到吗
Why not? Did you not hear me?
她是语言学系的助教
She's an assistant professor in the Linguistics Department, okay?
她们很辣
They're wild.
你到底为什么想去   是因为
Why do you want to come anyway? Because...
她是我表妹
...she's my cousin.
我是说  我们是一起长大的
I mean, we grew up together.
我们是家人  你知道吗  对我来说很重要
Family, you know? And all that's important to me.
好吧  我带你去
Okay, all right. I'll take you.
我去打电话给琼安
I'll go call Joan.
那真的是太棒了
Oh, that's nice.
家人应该要出席的
Family should be there.
这是她的婚礼  她一生中最快乐的日子
This is her wedding. Happiest day of her life.
我们等着瞧吧
We'll see. Ha, ha.
谢谢你请我吃午餐
Well, thank you for lunch.
什么  等一下  我以为你付了钱
What? Wait a minute, I didn't pay. I thought you paid.
很明显的  我们不必再掏钱买食物了
So apparently, we just don't pay for food anymore.
我没有看错吧  它还在那里
Do you see what I see? Huh! It's still there.
布雷曼太太一定是出去了
Mrs. Braverman must be out.
她可能出城去了  或许几个月后才会回来
She could be out of town. Maybe she'll be gone for months.
到时候  蛋糕一定坏了
By then, the cheesecake may have gone bad.
不能让她回来时看到坏掉的起司蛋糕
We don't want her to come back to bad cheesecake.
她可能会中毒死掉   我不希望发生那种事
No that could kill her. Well, we don't want that.
我们是在保护她
No so we're protecting her.
我们把它拿走  但是要快点
We should take it. But we should move quick.
为什么  我听到她在里面走动的声音
Why? Because I think I just heard her moving around in there.
快走  快走
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
天啊  是大卫
Oh, my God, that's David.
谁  那个科学家大卫
Who? David, the scientist guy.
我爱上了的那个大卫
David that I was in love with.
那个去了俄罗斯伤了我的心的大卫
David who went to Russia and broke my heart, David.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
只要一直念某人的名字  那个人就会转过身来
Oh, you say someone's name enough, they turn around.
菲比  大卫
Phoebe. David.
你在做什么   你不是在俄罗斯吗
What are you doing here? Aren't you supposed to be in Russia?
我到城里来开会
Yeah, I'm just in town for a conference.
天啊  你看起来美得出奇
Um, God, you look phenomenal.
喔
Well, ha, ha...
对
Yeah.
你看起来也很棒  你剪了头发吗
You look great too. Did you get a haircut?
对  我大概剪了三十次
Yeah. Well, I got like 3O of them.
是
Yeah.
听着  我要跟你坦诚一件事
Um, look, I got a confession to make. Uh-huh.
我希望能在这里遇到你
Um, I was hoping to run into you here.
我不知道该不该打电话给你  我只会在城里待几天
I didn't know that I should call or not. You know, I was only in town a few days...
我不想打扰你的生活
...and, you know, I didn't want to intrude on your life or anything like that,
我真的想见你
But I really wanted to see you...
但我不知道你要不要见我
...but I didn't know if you wanted to see me.
我当然想见你  我常常想到你
Of course I would want to see you. I think about you all the time.
真的吗  因为我也常常想到你
Really? Because I think about you all the time.
真的吗  明斯克有一座雕像
Really? There's a statue in Minsk...
让我常常想起你
...that reminds me of you so much.
实际上  那是列宁的雕像
I mean, um, it's actually of Lenin...
但有些角度看起来
...but, you know, at certain angles... Yeah.
总之  今晚你想跟我共进晚餐吗
Anyway, do you want to have dinner tonight?
好
Yes.
喔  不
Oh, no. Oh.
什么  我不能
Uh, what? I can't.
我不敢相信  我已经有约了  今天不行  明天可以吗
I can't believe I have plans. I can't. Can you do it tomorrow?
不行  再过几小时我就得离开了  我得赶回去
Uh, no, I have to go in a few hours. I have to be on the redeye.
听着  下次你到明斯克
Well, listen, you know, next time you're in Minsk, uh...
菲比  我能跟你谈一谈吗
Phoebe? Can I talk to you for a second? Uh-huh.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我今晚跟乔伊有约  所以呢  他会谅解的
Well, I have plans with Joey tonight. So? He'll understand.
不  他不会的  那根本不是重点
No, he won't. And that's not even the point.
摩妮卡  我教训他不该见色忘友
Monica, I made a whole speech about how you do not cancel plans with friends.
而现在呢   只因为可能是我真爱的人
And now, you know, what? Just because, potentially, the love of my life...
明天就要回俄罗斯了  我就应该改变我的想法
...comes back from Russia just for one night, I should change my beliefs?
我应该改变我的想法
I should change my beliefs.
不  如果失去了原则   我什么都不会有
No. No, no. If I don't have my principles, I don't have anything.
天啊  你太有说服力了
God, you are so strong.
或许我可以赶快跟乔伊吃完晚餐  然后九点跟大卫见面
Or I should rush through dinner with Joey and I could meet David at 9.
我的天啊  真的是太棒了
Oh, my God, that is so good.
我吃饱了  但我知道  如果我现在停下来
I'm full. And yet I know if I stop eating this...
我会后悔的
...I'll regret it.
嘿  你们在吃什么
Hey, what have you got there?
那是  喔
Oh, it's, um...
豆腐蛋糕  你要吃一点吗
it's tofu cake. Do you want some? Aah.
今晚你要做什么
What are you doing tonight? Huh?
兄弟
Uh. Dude. Dude.
对不起  我跟菲比有约
Sorry. Uh, I got those plans with Phoebe.
真的  摩妮卡说她九点有约会
Oh, really? Uh, Monica said she had a date at 9.
什么  今晚  摩妮卡是那么说的
What? Tonight? That's what Monica said.
她教训了我一顿
After she gave me that big speech...
却同时约了我跟她的男伴
...she goes and makes a date on the same night she has plans with me'?
她想草草解决 "大爹地"
I think she's trying to pull a fast one on Big Daddy.
好了  我们的位置应该是这一桌
Oh here, I think this is us. Yeah.
还座位有限  屁话
Limited seating, my ass.
我们来看看  谁被邀请了
Let's just see who made the cut.
嗨  我是摩妮卡盖勒
Hi. Hi. I'm Monica Geller.
你们跟新人是什么关系   我是芬妮以前的同事
How do you know the bride and groom? I worked with Frannie.
以前的同事  以前
Used to work with her. Used to.
我是她的亲戚却没有被邀请
I'm a relative and I didn't get invited, okay?
我是她的血亲  血
A blood relative. Blood.
别在陌生人面前提到 "血"
Stop saying "blood" to strangers.
你呢  你跟快乐的新人是什么关系
So how about you? How do you know the happy couple?
我们是他们的大学同学  现在是他们的邻居
We went to college with both of them. And now we live next door.
好吧  你还够格
Okay, you're fine.
你们要点菜了吗  是的
Hey. Are you guys ready? Hey. Yes.
我要沙拉  特调酱汁  给我水就好了
I will have a green salad, urn, house dressing and water's fine.
你呢  先生
Okay. And for you, sir?
对  慢烤鲑鱼
Yeah. This slow-roasted salmon...
那到底有多慢呢
...just how slow are we talkin' here?
它已经烤好了
It's already been roasted.
那我不要了  麻烦你  再告诉我一次今日特餐
Oh, then no. Maybe I should hear those specials again.
乔伊  我们已经听了三次
Oh, Joey, we've heard the specials three times, okay?
有烤肋排  鬼头刀鱼  跟特制龙虾饺子
There's prime rib, mahi-mahi and a very special lobster ravioli.
事实上我们没有饺子了  那我们得重来一次
Actually, we're out of the lobster ravioli. Oh, well, that changes everything.
你知道吗  菲比
You know what, Pheebs? Uh-huh.
之前你说的话是对的  朋友太重要了
You were right before. Friends are so important.
对  我很聪明  我知道
Yeah, I'm very wise. I know.
你知道我想做什么吗
You know what I really want?
什么  我想花时间跟你长谈
What? ls to have a long, long talk.
你知道吗   多告诉我一点人生道理
You know? Get Joey out on the open road and really open him up.
可以点菜了吗  可以
Any progress? Yes.
我要点龙虾饺子
I will have the lobster ravioli.
天啊  乔伊  这得花一辈子的时间
God, Joey, this is taking forever.
现在干嘛这么急   喔
What's the rush? Well...
我有个约会
...I just have, you know, an appointment.
它非常重要
And it's very important.
怎么说
What is it?
喔
Well...
我约了一个男人
...it's a date.
你约了男人  不  不  菲比  你一定弄错了
A date? No, no, Pheebs, you must be mistaken...
因为你不能跟男人约会的同时
...because you wouldn't schedule a date...
又跟朋友约吃饭
...on the night you have plans with a friend.
别让我觉得内疚
Come on. Don't make me feel badly about this.
不  我就是要那么做
No, I'm gonna.
好吧  我跟那个女孩出去
That's right. Yeah, you made me feel really guilty...
你让我觉得非常内疚
...about going outwith that girl.
好像我做了什么可怕的事  菲比  现在你也那么做
Like I did something terrible to you. Now, Pheebs, you're doing the same thing.
我才不呢   这个完全不一样
That's not the same thing. This is totally different.
我跟大卫有约  你还记得科学家大卫吗
This is with David. Remember David, the scientist guy?
对我来说他非常特别
Okay, he's very special to me.
那晚我约的女孩也很特别
Okay, well, my girl from the other night was special.
她也是个科学家
She was a scientist too.
是吗  她高中毕业
She was? Well, she graduated high school.
随便啦  你知道吗
Okay, whatever. Know what?
我没时间跟你讲道理
I don't have time to convince you.
他只会在这里待4个小时  我得去见他
He's only here for four hours and I'm gonna go see him.
好吧  对  对
Fine. Fine! Yeah. Yeah.
你还在这里做什么  我说过了  龙虾饺子
What are you still doing here? I told you, lobster ravioli.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
我正要离开  我以为你不会来了
Oh, I was just about to leave. I didn't think you were coming.
我绝不会错过这次约会
Oh, I wouldn't have missed this. Ha, ha.
我很高兴你能来
Well, I'm very glad you're here.
你是个绅士
Oh, you're such a gentleman.
来吧  到我家去
Come on, we're going to my place.
你想一个人独吞起司蛋糕
Are you eating the cheesecake without me?
只要你现在能吹出口哨  我就给你一百块钱
I will give you $100 to whistle right now.
你怎么可以不管我  一个人独吞
How can you eat the cheesecake without me?
你会怎么做呢
What are you gonna do?
告诉摩妮卡或乔伊  不  你得把一切都告诉他们
Gonna run and tell Monica or Joey? No, you'd have to tell them what we did.
我们是甜点小偷  我们犯了法
We are dessert stealers. We are living outside the law.
知道吗  我不能让你跟蛋糕独处
You know what? I don't trust you with this cake anymore!
我先发现它的  我要把它拿回来  什么
And I got it first, and I'm taking it back. What?
什么  不  不  对
What? Oh, no, you don't. Oh, yes.
你以为我就能相信你吗
You think I trust you with it?
不  我们平分它  你一半  我一半
We're gonna split it. You take half, I take half.
那不公平   你已经吃掉一点了
That's not fair. You had some.
我想摩妮卡一定想知道
Oh, you know what? I think Monica would be very interested to know...
你说她做的起司蛋糕 "又干又粗"
...that you called her cheesecake dry and mealy.
我们用什么来切蛋糕呢
What do we use to split it? Okay.
好了  各人拿一块
All right, pick a half. Okay.
这块比较大
Well, this side looks bigger. Mm-hm.
但这块饼干比较多
Uh, but there's more crust on this side.
或许我该量一下
Yeah. So maybe if I measure it--
拜托  快挑一块
For God's sake, pick a piece.
好吧  我挑那块  那块比较小
All right, I pick that one. So the smaller piece.
好了  拿去吧
Okay. There you go.
好好享受你的蛋糕吧  我的朋友  因为大势已定
Enjoy your half, my friend. But that is it.
我不会跟你分  或跟你换   别哭着跑来找我
No sharing, no switching, and don't come crying to me...
如果你一下子就把蛋糕都吃完了
...if you eat your piece too fast.
好
Oh!
你要给我点蛋糕吗  不
You gonna give me some of your piece? Oh, no.
我不会跟你分  或跟你换   别哭着跑来找我
No switching, no sharing. And don't come crying to me.
我要坐在这里  花一整天好好享用我的蛋糕
Ha, ha. I may just sit here and have my cake all day.
我要坐在走廊上吃我的
Just sit here in the hallway and eat my--
罗斯  甜心
Ross, sweetheart.
嘿  米莉阿姨
Oh, hey, Aunt Millie.
这个婚礼很温馨吧  对对  没错
Isn't it a beautiful wedding? Yes. Yes, it is.
她每次都亲嘴巴
Every time, on the lips.
为什么  为什么要亲嘴巴
Why? Why on the lips?
芬妮在那边  她看到我一定会很高兴吧
There's Frannie. Won't she be happy to see me?
等等  你得乖乖的  好吗
Now, wait a minute. You be nice, all right?
我不是带你来欺负她的
I didn't bring you here so you could ambush her.
芬妮把你的《花花公子》拿给妈妈看
Frannie was the one who found your Playboys and showed them to Mom.
那个死小孩
That bitch.
摩妮卡  什么
Monica. What--?
我在这里做什么  你看到我很惊讶吗
Am I doing here? Surprised to see me?
罗斯带我来的  你还喜欢吗
Ross brought me. How do you like that?
芬妮  恭喜
Hi, Frannie. Congratulations.
你邀请我的哥哥  我的家人  却不邀请我  为什么
You invite my brother, you invite my whole family, and not me? Why?
你为什么不希望我来
Why wouldn't you want me at your wedding?
我做了什么吗
What could I have possibly done?
史都华
Stuart.
我相信你认识我丈夫
I believe you know my husband.
问题应该是   你把上了"谁"
So it's really a question of "who" could you have possibly done.
我讨厌这样   但我得走了
I hate this, but I have to go. Mm-hm.
我不能错过飞机
I can't miss my flight.
我敢说下一班飞往明斯克的飞机是在
Are you sure? I bet there's another flight to Minsk in--
七月
July
那真的好窝心  它是什么意思
That's really beautiful. What does it mean?
"请帮我把杯子洗干净"
"Please clean my beakers."
我不常离开实验室
I don't get out of the lab much.
我以为它有别的意思
I thought it meant something else.
对   事实上  我想说
Yeah, well, I really actually wanted to say, um...
那个
...that.
我想或许我不该说  因为
But, urn, I figured I probably shouldn't because...
我得离开
...you know, I have to leave.
不  你说的对  别说
Hmm. No, you're right. Don't say it.
但我真的那么想
I do, though.
我也是
I do too.
再见  菲比
Well, bye, Phoebe.
现在不是时候  乔伊   明天你可以骂我
Okay, now's not the time, Joey, all right? You can yell at me tomorrow.
等一下  不  不  菲比  我不会骂你
No, no. No, Pheebs. I'm not gonna yell at you.
我只是开始想到你跟大卫
I just started thinking about you and David...
我记得他第一次离开时  你是多难过
...and I remember how bummed you were the first time he left.
菲比  过来
Oh, Pheebs, come here.
你还好吧  不  我一点都不好
Are you okay? No, I'm not okay.
我唯一喜欢的男人要去明斯克
The only guy I've ever been crazy about is going to Minsk...
或许我永远都不会再见到他
...and I may never see him again.
你可以去看他
Hey, you could always visit him.
对   你以为他们会给我护照
Oh, right. Like they're gonna let me have a passport.
有什么我可以帮忙的吗   什么都行
Anything I can do? Whatever you need.
喔
Well, now...
如果你可以比他先蒸馏出副原子粒子
...if you achieve positronic distillation of subatomic particles before he does...
他就可以回来了
...then he could come back.
我可以试试看
I could give it a shot.
你看  有一小块没有沾到地板
Oh, look. There's a piece that doesn't have floor on it.
别越界  快点
Stick to your side. Come on, now.
好了  我们要吃什么
All right, what are we having?
等一下  我忘了拿披肩
Oh, wait, I forgot my wrap.
好吧   你在这里等我
Oh, okay, wait here.
嗨  甜心  你要走了吗
Hi, sweetie. Are you leaving?
喔  亲阿姨一下  快点
Well-Give us a kiss. Come on.
为什么  为什么要亲嘴巴
Why? Why on the lips?